Rewarding teachers, let's go, let's go!
That's what I'm talking about.
Today, I'm going to take the liberty of filming the Galgal Channel.
I've taken the liberty of filming it.
I haven't reported this to the person in charge yet.
I'm taking pictures without permission, but I'd like you to use them.
I've renewed the first one without permission.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry, it didn't work.
This is the renewal of the Galgal Channel.
Thank you very much.
I'm doing this all on my own.
So what's today?
Today is the first day of the Girls Girls Girls Live Tour 2023 Activate in Sapporo.
On the third day, only Clear and I are still left.
We went to the EXPG STUDIO Sapporo performance.
We're going to do a choreography or update today.
I hope we can enjoy Sapporo a little before or after the show.
I hope that's okay.
I'm taking some videos today.
First of all, we went to Nijo Market.
Seafood?
Like a market in Tokyo.
It's like a resin in Tokyo.
I guess there is a market there.
I think I'll go there for breakfast first.
Good night.
Wow!
This looks delicious.
It's so good!
Bon appétit!
I'll have this for breakfast, and I'll have this for breakfast, and I'll have this for breakfast.
It tastes so good!
Hot.
What's wrong? What's wrong? What's wrong?
What's wrong? What's up?
Oh, there you are.
I don't know about you, but...
It's a surprise.
It's really good.
Help me out with the temperature.
This is Yokan's favorite!
This is YOKAN's favorite, too, from a long time ago.
I've always wanted a cup with sushi written on it like this.
I've always wanted a cup like this.
That's nice.
I want one.
It's cute.
You know...
You had lunch with Momo, right?
Yeah.
I was so surprised at how little conversation we had.
That's usual.
Like frogs.
Frogs.
But they're the top two things I can't talk about.
With Momo...
I'm really not talking about that.
He said the store is different.
What?
But I thought it was okay.
Yeah.
I thought that's what Momo must be thinking.
For the first time in my life, for the first time in my life.
Wasabi stuck in my nose.
Oh, you get wasabi stuck in your nose?
It's like this.
There's something coming up...
When you taste the wasabi in the upper part of your nose, it's like...
It's a problem of eating, isn't it?
I like cat's tongue.
Yeah, like a cat's tongue.
What did you say?
Wasabi tongue.
Why?
Because I have a cat tongue. It's like a wasabi tongue.
I'm sorry if you didn't get that.
I don't mind at all.
I hope you know that I mean that sincerely.
I know.
I really do.
I'm doing a lot of Coke recipes this time.
I hope I don't give away too much.
I won't say a little bit.
But seriously.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. What was that? You just went to spill it.
So you're going to spill it when you're trying to hide it, too?
I must have made a mistake.
Yes, please.
The recipe for Coke.
He returns it so much!
He's always giving it back to me. That's a first.
It's the first time. They're all so quick to catch on.
But that's exactly what I'm talking about.
And the director, the guy who was in charge of the production...
He said it was really nice.
I wonder if that's true.
I'm pretty hungry.
Just one is fine.
I'm too greedy, I guess.
I'm not sure if it's too much. I thought so, but...
What's not enough?
Oh.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's why
I bought a soft serve ice cream from Snow Brand Parla!
Wow, it looks so good!
Delicious!
So rich!
It's amazing!
Are you a cone man or a cup man?
I prefer cups.
What about you?
Which one are you?
Which one?
Go to Nijo Ishiba.
Go to the TV tower.
Snow Brand.
From here...
I'm going to Sapporo Port.
I think I'll go see everyone.
I'll see you later.
Yes, so we've arrived at EXPG STUDIO Sapporo!
Okay, what are we going to do now?
We are going to release our new album on December 20th.
Accelerate, which will be released on December 20.
EXPG STUDIO Sapporo kids to sing the chorus part of the song "Dotch".
I'm going to give a lecture to the kids at EXPG STUDIO Sapporo on the chorus of the song!
It's really easy, so to be honest, I think it's so easy that you can do it even if you watch the video.
I think it's so easy that you can go there even if you watch the video.
I hope you guys can learn the notes together.
I'd love to learn it with you guys.
I'm going to give a dance lecture.
It's been a while since I've been a teacher.
It's been too long.
It's been about 3 years since we've been back to Sapporo.
We did it last time in Sapporo.
I'm sure some of you know who I am.
So I'm off to Sapporo.
One, two, three...
Thank you for your hard work.
Five, four.
And now, lift the leg.
Are you okay? Yes, I'm fine.
Here we are.
You're here.
Stay.
Which way?
Soon.
This hand...
On the back.
The back light.
Ready!
One, two, three, four.
Let me see.
Corona
Free
Pause
This video is the best for some reason lawn
inspired
I had it
s Там